[{"answer": "Well, there's always an opportunity to look things over and determine that there could possibly be another way that it could have been done.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Do you believe that it was all completely justified or do you think it was another way perhaps of resolving this without your friend being killed?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, I think clearly what has to happened is we rely on the (inaudible) training, and let this clarified for the record if I could, Pierce, is I'm with National Country Sheriffs Department, not the police department.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "And, does any of that in the end come into play though, if you're guarding the white house or the capitol itself because it could be (ph) you could be on such ready alert any kind of attack and really have time to think is this person, you know, a harmless woman who is suffering some form of depression or is she a terrorist?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you can always look at the tape afterwards and say there're things we can learn from this.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "I kind know where (ph) come from here, but is anything you heard so far in the show giving you any cause to post about your absolute certainty that the police did everything completely correctly here?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, it does give you something to think about.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Knowing so much more makes more complicated and it makes my heartstrings get togged a little bit but the police didn't have the benefit of knowing this woman's history, her background, they didn't even know whether or not she had a gun.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "What is your reaction now we know you so much more?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, first of all those Capitol police officers deserved our thanks and our appreciation in every bit of the standing ovation we gave them because they lay their lives on the line for us every single day and we worked in a building that is one of the most high value targets in the entire world.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Obviously, it's very complicated and you don't want to be too critical of the police, what do you think?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "... even this weekend has taken the website down for repairs.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Debbie?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "... borrowing $ 2 billion a day is not a fiscally responsible ...", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Pierce, can I say something else?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "The idea that John Boehner, he doesn't working in space.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "(Inaudible) KellyAnne?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Because Barack Obama won't show up.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Why doesn't he get into a bar with Barack Obama and do some business?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "There is no doubt.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Tea Party led by Ted Cruz has led all this from start to finish?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Six days.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "When is this going to end, very quickly?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "October 17th.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "We're not averse (ph) calling.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "If President Rouhani picked the telephone up and called you, would you take that call?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "The military action is not a goal, it's a means.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Were you happy that having set the red line as President Obama did about the use of chemical weapons, he didn't then take military action?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "No, I want to see it back with action.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "You're not buying the new friendlier face of Iran's edition?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "It would mean something if he would take, it would mean nothing if they continue their nuclear weapons program.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Does it mean anything that he at least had taken that step?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "ETANYAHU: It was great.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "What were you thinking when you did that interview and was it a successful as you hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, simply put Piers, that Iran will have to get nuclear weapons.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you have your own red line when it comes to Iran, and if so, what is it?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I wouldn't hesitate at all.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Would you hesitate to take military action?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "ETANYAHU: Well, Rouhani openly says that he is deceiving.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Can you envisage that kind of meeting with, say, Rouhani?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "I was told by a very good source that your very first meeting with President Obama was running as (ph) a senator and it was in Washington Airport and you literally went often to a little side room?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "You were the leader of the opposition?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Look, he's trying to do the best he can for the United States.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Has he realized his potential and what you do you think of him as a leader for the Israeli perspective?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "It's a big problem obviously because it's an unstable region, and we're stable because we're based on very solid foundations and we're people that been - that's been attached to this landfall since the time of Abraham.", "docId": "131004pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Do you feel more vulnerable as a result of over turmoil and how do you see it all playing out?", "qSentId": 541}]